so i just want to understand because i keep seeing folks be like i'm running for senate
i'm running for governor i'm running for prom queen in a system that they have said exponentially
is fucked up so is and you're not gonna win none of you all who are running for any of
these positions are gonna win none of you anti-zionists are gonna win this is not me being
a hater it's just that if you're paying attention you understand that all of this is set up and it's
going further and further and further into the crevasse my favorite episode of 30 rock where
the zionism thrives so why why do you think that there's fair elections in order for you to win
you'd have to play as dirty as those people and you know for what it's worth find a way to rig the
shit so is it the running that's that's like the revolutionary part of this is it just like i'm
just running to shake shit up i guess that's what that's what it is it's like the idea that if you
if you run you you show people that there's other options and my take is the options are still within
the system the system that needs to end
have you been away